<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jarelion</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 21:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 21:32:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>kaytranada</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/kaytranada-album-interview-99-percent.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;kaytranada-album-interview-99-percent.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;is-one-of-the-best-albums-of-the-year&quot;&gt;99.9% is one of the best albums of the year.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kay’s inventive percussion keeps the album upbeat, but it’s often a dreamy, mellow listen, perhaps a result of the producer’s effort to broaden perceptions of his capabilities. Many of the featured collaborators, including Phonte, Syd, and Anderson .Paak, are hip-hop adjacent artists who have refused to be constrained by the dogmas of the genre, something that seems to have inspired Kay. Syd and Phonte in particular, have helped to define a contemporary, melodic take on funk, combining soul, R&amp;amp;B, and a dash of electronica. Their features, “One Too Many” and “You’re the One,” on which Kay showcases his love for warmly shimmering synths, are two of the album’s strongest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/kaytranada-album-interview-99-percent-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;kaytranada-album-interview-99-percent-1.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/kaytranada-album-interview-99-percent-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;kaytranada-album-interview-99-percent-2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only four of the album’s fifteen tracks do not feature a guest, but even without any company, Kaytranada displays plenty of range. His most impressive solo cut is “Lite Spots,” a rework of the Brazilian singer Gal Costa’s 1973 track, “Pontos De Luz.” Kay takes advantage of the abrupt shifts in tempo in Costa’s original vocal, assembling a circle of handclaps and other percussive quirks to maximize the song’s potential as a house party special.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/title/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/title/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
